shoulder_oian_quiz = [
    {"question": "What is the origin of Deltoid?", "options": ["Clavicle and scapula", "Supraspinous fossa of scapula", "Lateral border of scapula"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Deltoid?", "options": ["Distal phalanges of fingers", "Deltoid tuberosity of humerus", "Greater tubercle of humerus"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Deltoid?", "options": ["Laterally rotates arm", "Flexes arm", "Abducts arm"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Deltoid?", "options": ["Axillary nerve", "Suprascapular nerve", "Radial nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Supraspinatus?", "options": ["Lateral border of scapula", "Clavicle and scapula", "Supraspinous fossa of scapula"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Supraspinatus?", "options": ["Greater tubercle of humerus", "Radial tuberosity", "Olecranon process of ulna"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Supraspinatus?", "options": ["Abducts arm", "Flexes arm", "Adducts arm"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Supraspinatus?", "options": ["Axillary nerve", "Suprascapular nerve", "Radial nerve"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Infraspinatus?", "options": ["Infraspinous fossa of scapula", "Lateral border of scapula", "Clavicle and scapula"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Infraspinatus?", "options": ["Olecranon process of ulna", "Greater tubercle of humerus", "Deltoid tuberosity of humerus"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Infraspinatus?", "options": ["Laterally rotates arm", "Abducts arm", "Flexes arm"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Infraspinatus?", "options": ["Suprascapular nerve", "Radial nerve", "Axillary nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Teres Minor?", "options": ["Lateral border of scapula", "Infraspinous fossa of scapula", "Clavicle and scapula"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Teres Minor?", "options": ["Greater tubercle of humerus", "Deltoid tuberosity of humerus", "Olecranon process of ulna"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Teres Minor?", "options": ["Adducts arm", "Laterally rotates arm", "Flexes arm"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Teres Minor?", "options": ["Axillary nerve", "Radial nerve", "Suprascapular nerve"], "answer": "a"}
]
